<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">       Medical simulation provides an opportunity for the learners to experience the complexity of the clinical settings.</statement>
     <statement id="2">       I need a fully-equipped simulation center to provide an effective simulation session </statement>
     <statement id="3">       I can provide an effective simulation with a low budget.</statement>
     <statement id="4">       Medical simulation prepares the trainees for what they will face as healthcare providers in real life.</statement>
     <statement id="5">       I find it difficult to obtain the resources necessary to train learners using medical simulation.</statement>
     <statement id="6">       Using medical simulation as a teaching method should always be a part of the curriculum.</statement>
     <statement id="7">       Faculty using medical simulation require training to conduct effective sessions.</statement>
     <statement id="8">       Medical simulation greatly enhances the learners' soft skills (communication, leadership, teamwork).</statement>
     <statement id="9">       Medical simulation requires a lot of work and effort to conduct.</statement>
     <statement id="10">      Using medical simulation as an assessment tool is essential for assessing practical and clinical skills.</statement>
     <statement id="11">      The current state of support provided by my college to simulation education is a major hindrance.</statement>
     <statement id="12">      Only a skilled facilitator can motivate and engage learners with the simulated scenario.</statement>
     <statement id="13">      Educational leaders support for simulation-based teaching is important for the implementation of effective simulation activities.</statement>
     <statement id="14">      High-fidelity manikins are needed to conduct an effective simulation session.</statement>
     <statement id="15">      Even though students say it was very useful to them, we may not necessarily have seen that translate in the clinical setting.</statement>
     <statement id="16">      Medical simulation sessions are a scheduling nightmare.</statement>
     <statement id="17">      Producing a believable proper scenario requires a lot of time in the laboratory.</statement>
     <statement id="18">      To achieve wide use of simulation, we need more resources that help us reach different kind of scenarios.</statement>
     <statement id="19">      Using simulation reduces the students’ stress when transitioning to the clinical setting.</statement>
     <statement id="20">      Training on medical simulation models and manikins is the best choice for teaching psychomotor skills.</statement>
     <statement id="21">      Medical simulation can replace bedside training.</statement>
     <statement id="22">      Simulations help students learn how to collaborate with members of an interprofessional team.</statement>
     <statement id="23">      The learning curve to use simulation technology for teaching is a huge obstacle on the faculty.</statement>
     <statement id="24">      Limitations on space given for simulation make it difficult to fully simulate the clinical experience.</statement>
     <statement id="25">      An effective simulation does not need many resources. A good educator can work with any resources available.</statement>
     <statement id="26">      Because of simulation, we now make better use of the learning time students have in the clinical setting.</statement>
     <statement id="27">      Simulation teaching creates a highly realistic, yet safe and reproducible learning environment.</statement>
     <statement id="28">      We need more clinical instructors who have received proper training on the use of medical simulation.</statement>
     <statement id="29">      I believe constructing simulation sessions and courses help in the settings of remediation. </statement>
     <statement id="30">      Simulation fills the gap because students will not always have a chance to perform skills in clinical settings.</statement>
     <statement id="31">      A big disadvantage of simulators is that students cannot tell if they are hurting them; therefore, reduces students' empathy when dealing with patients.</statement>
     <statement id="32">      Lack of human resources in our program hinders a full integration of simulation-based learning in the curriculum. </statement>
     <statement id="33">      We must use medical simulation more often (at least once a month) to achieve its benefits. </statement>
     <statement id="34">      I have a positive attitude toward using simulation for medical education.  </statement>
     <statement id="35">      Integrating simulation into the curriculum will require more from me than traditional teaching. </statement>
     <statement id="36">      Learning by using simulation can stand in the way of providing a standardized teaching experience for all students. </statement>
     <statement id="37">      You cannot conduct effective simulation-based learning without being able to provide an appropriate feedback.  </statement>
     <statement id="38">      Having supporting staff is essential for the growth and wide use of medical simulation.  </statement>
     <statement id="39">      Simulation teaching can completely overcome the problem of uncooperative patients during the practice experience. </statement>
     <statement id="40">      Simulation teaching minimizes the needed effort put in by educators in the clinical setting. </statement>
     <statement id="41">      Medical simulation teaching should be minimum because it is very time-consuming. </statement>
     <statement id="42">      The enormous number of students and limited opportunities to interact with patients calls for increasing the use of simulation teaching. </statement>
     <statement id="43">      A healthcare educator must be trained to conduct an effective simulation-based learning. </statement>
     <statement id="44">      Securing funds is the only way to improve the current use of medical simulation. </statement>
   </statements>